<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mildly Boring</title><link>https://mildlyboring.com/</link><description>Recent content on Mildly Boring</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Fahad Hossain</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 21:50:17 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mildlyboring.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello, Blog (again) 🙄</title><link>https://mildlyboring.com/post/hello-blog-again/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 21:50:17 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://mildlyboring.com/post/hello-blog-again/</guid><description>This is the nth time I&amp;rsquo;ve switched blogging platforms.
So, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to articulate why I switch these things so often.
I ❤️ Markdown Markdown is one of those things that I&amp;rsquo;ve liked ever since the first time I used it.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, Markdown is a really simple way of writing rich text using nothing more than a handful of characters to denote formatting. The format is super-simple and in my opinion one of the best ways to write content such as this blog post.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://mildlyboring.com/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mildlyboring.com/about/</guid><description>Hi 👋, I&amp;rsquo;m Fahad (/fähɑð/). GitHub LinkedIn I&amp;rsquo;m a Software Engineer from Dhaka, Bangladesh. I specialize in creating performant and scalable reactive web apps using React and Node. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working at Digital Healthcare Solutions (formerly Telenor Health). I&amp;rsquo;m also in the process of completing my undergrad at AIUB. I enjoy learning about new technology (languages/frameworks/libraries/syntax&amp;hellip;) and I&amp;rsquo;m usually willing to pay the early-adopter tax if I think the tech is awesome.</description></item><item><title>The Introduction. A Fool's Guide To Writing Functional JS (Part 1)</title><link>https://mildlyboring.com/post/functional-js-part-1-introduction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 18:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mildlyboring.com/post/functional-js-part-1-introduction/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re a developer going about your day writing loops and pushing and deleting stuff from arrays and what not. And then some day you think 🤔
maybe I should test my code&amp;hellip;
&amp;ldquo;Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too hard&amp;rdquo;, you say.
And then you get started, you learn the basics of unit testing and even write some tests. But as soon as your code gets a bit more complex, it starts to seem like almost impossible to test.</description></item></channel></rss>